

VALENTINA MORALES

COMPUTER ENGINEER / WEB DEVELOPER

Phone:

+58 424-6571181

Email:

valencibel@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/v-morales

Location:

Maracaibo, Venezuela

WORK HISTORY

Frontend Developer (Remote)

FORCAST, CHILE SEPT 2019 - FEB 2020

- Managed project tasks and kept a constant feedback with the development team.
- · Created content for the web site in development.
- Refactored and documented the web page Frontend components.

Web Developer

INSITE, VENEZUELA SEPT 2018 - SEPT 2019

- Developed and desgined web applications and page views.
- User Experience (UX).
- Fixed bugs from existing websites.
- Refactored and documented the web page Frontend components and Backend endpoints.

Intern

INSITE, VENEZUELA JULY 2018 - SEPT 2018

- First level technical support.
- Basic level consulting on new features and implementations on web system.
- Low fidelity prototyping of new feature form on web platform.

PROFILE

I'm a computer engineer, able to apply my knowledge, experience and skills to develop professionally and integrally, with excellent communication skills, proactive thinking, open and capable of assuming new challenges. During my time at the University I learned about different areas of software development, the most relevant subject-matters of the syllabus for my formation as a professional I can name Web Development I and II, Object Oriented Programming, Systems Audit, Software Engineering I and II, and Mobile Device Programming.

EDUCATION

Universidad Rafael Urdaneta

Maracaibo, Venezuela Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering (2015 - 2019)

Colegio La Presentación

Maracaibo, Venezuela High School Diploma (2009 - 2014)

COURSES

 Master en JavaScript: Aprender JS, jQuery, Angular, NodeJS (2021) - UDEMY

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Typescript
- Angular
- ReactJS
- MYSQL

TOOLS

- Trello
- GIT
- GitHub/GitLab

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native).
- English (Intermediate).